http://www.aiag.org/terms-of-use

Terms of Use
These Terms of Use were last modified on May 24, 2018.
These terms of use (“Terms of Use”) are an agreement between you and Automotive Industry Action Group, a Michigan nonprofit corporation, ("AIAG", "we" or "us") and govern your access to and use of the following resources.
All goods, services, and software available through the web domain www.aiag.org and any applications marketed or provided through that domain;
All other electronic resources provided by AIAG.
Each such resource including all content, functionality and services offered on or through each resource, is a “Resource.”
“You,” “yours,” and similar words mean the user of a Resource. If a Resource is used by an individual, for, or on behalf of, an organization, (a) “you,” “yours,” and similar words mean the individual and the organization jointly and severally, (b) the individual binds the organization to these Terms or Use, and (c) the individual represents and warrants to AIAG and its licensors that the individual has the authority to bind the organization.
Please read these Terms of Use carefully before using any Resource. By using any Resource, or by clicking to accept these Terms of Use when the option is made available to you, you accept and agree to these Terms of Use and our Privacy Policy found at http://www.aiag.org/privacy-policy (the “Privacy Policy”). If you do not agree to these Terms of Use or the Privacy Policy, do not use any Resource.
Changes to These Terms of Use
We may revise and update these Terms of Use from time to time in our sole discretion. All changes are effective immediately when we post them and apply to all subsequent access to and use of a Resource. Your continued use of a Resource following the posting of changes means that you accept and agree to the changes. You are expected to check these Terms of Use regularly so that you are aware of any changes.
Resource Access and Use
Access to, and use of, each Resource is limited to users permitted by AIAG.  AIAG may limit or deny access at AIAG’s discretion if you violate these Terms of Use.
All information that you provide when you register or otherwise begin using any Resource must be correct, current and complete. All information you provide is governed by the Privacy Policy and you consent to all actions we take with respect to this information consistent with the Privacy Policy, including any revisions to the Privacy Policy.
If you choose, or are provided with, a user name, password, or other information as part of our access or security procedures, you must treat such information as confidential, and you must not disclose it to any other person or entity. You acknowledge that your account is personal to you, and you agree not to provide any other person with access to any Resource or portions of it using your user name, password or other security information. You must notify us immediately of any unauthorized access to or use of your user name or password or any other breach of security.
Until you notify us otherwise and we have had a commercially reasonable time to respond to your notice, we may, and will, assume that every transaction entered into, every authorization received, and every act or omission undertaken using your username and password are fully authorized by you.
We may withdraw or amend any Resource, and any service or material provided on any Resource, at any time in our sole discretion and without notice. We will not be liable if, for any reason, all or any part of any Resource is unavailable at any time or for any period.
You may use a Resource only for lawful purposes and in accordance with these Terms of Use. You will not use any Resource:
In any way that violates any applicable law or regulation.
To send or cause to be sent any advertising or promotional material, including any "junk mail", "chain letter", "spam" or similar solicitation.
To impersonate or attempt to impersonate AIAG, a AIAG employee, another user or any other person or entity (including, without limitation, by using e-mail addresses or screen names associated with any such person or entity).
To engage in any other conduct that restricts or inhibits anyone's use or enjoyment of a Resource, or that, as determined by us, may harm AIAG, users of any Resource or others.
In any manner that could disable, overburden, damage, or impair any Resource or interfere with any other party's use of a Resource.
Additionally, you may not:
Use any robot, spider, or other automatic device, process or means to access any Resource for any purpose, including monitoring or copying any of the material on any Resource.
Copy, reverse-engineer, attempt to discover or derive the source code of any Resource.
Provide any Resource to a third party, whether for compensation or otherwise, whether as part of a service bureau or otherwise.
Use parallel sessions, virtual users, or any other means that would allow the utilization of a resource at a rate or intensity, or with an efficiency, greater than that of an unaided human operator of the Resource.
Introduce any virus, Trojan horse, worm, logic bomb, spyware or other malicious or other harmful or malicious code or other material.
Attempt to gain unauthorized access to, interfere with, damage or disrupt any part of a Resource, the server on which any Resource is stored, or any network, server, computer, equipment or database connected to any Resource.
Attack any Resource using a denial-of-service attack or a distributed denial-of-service attack.
Otherwise attempt to interfere with the proper working of any Resource.
Export any Resource to, or use any Resource in, any jurisdiction in which the same is prohibited and/or in violation of any US or other export regulation.
Monitor any network or other traffic to, from, or on any Resource other than your own.
Benchmark any Resource against any other good, service, or software or provide the results of any such benchmarking to any third party.
Ownership of the Resource(s)
As between you and AIAG, each Resource and all of its content, features, and functionality are owned by AIAG, its licensors, or other providers of such material and is protected by United States and international copyright (© 2018 AIAG, its licensors, or other providers of such material), trademark, patent, trade secret and other law relating to intellectual property or other proprietary rights.
Information Sharing and User Contributions
A Resource may allow sharing of information in many ways, such as personal profiles, activity feeds, blog posts, discussions, polls, embedding, direct messaging features, and other interactive features that allow users to post, submit, publish, display or transmit ("submit") content or materials for viewing by AIAG, other users, or the public (each such item being a "User Contribution") on or through a Resource.
We do not claim ownership of your User Contributions.  However, by submitting any User Contribution to any Resource, you grant to us a worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable, nonexclusive, transferrable, sublicensable right and license to use, reproduce, modify, perform, display, distribute, publish, transmit, and process the User Contribution for any purpose related to any Resource without compensation to you or others.  User Contributions that you submit may be seen by other users.  Where we have made settings available, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to honor the choices you make about who can see your User Contributions.
With respect to any User Contributions you submit, you represent and warrant that you have the right to submit such User Contributions and to grant the right and license granted above.  You understand and acknowledge that you, and not AIAG, are fully responsible for the legality, reliability, accuracy and appropriateness of all User Contributions you submit.
You will not submit any User Contribution that does not comply with all applicable federal, state, local and international laws and regulations and the following standards (our “Content Standards”):
User Contributions must not contain any material that is defamatory, obscene, indecent, abusive, offensive, harassing, violent, hateful, inflammatory, or otherwise objectionable.
User Contributions must not be, or promote, sexually explicit or pornographic material, violence, or discrimination based on race, sex, religion, nationality, disability, sexual orientation, sexual identity, age, height or weight.
User Contributions must not infringe any patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright or other intellectual property or other proprietary right.
User Contributions must not violate the legal rights (including the rights of publicity and privacy) of others or contain any material that could give rise to any civil or criminal liability under applicable laws or regulations or that otherwise may be in conflict with these Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy.
User Contributions must not be likely to deceive any person.
User Contributions must not promote any illegal activity, or advocate, promote or assist any unlawful act.
User Contributions must not impersonate any person, or misrepresent your identity or affiliation with any person or organization.
User Contributions must not involve commercial activities or sales, such as contests, sweepstakes and other sales promotions, barter, or advertising.
User Contributions must not give the impression that they emanate from or are endorsed by us or any other person or entity if that is not the case.
AIAG may permit other users of a Resource to re-publish or otherwise use your User Contributions outside the scope of a Resource for purposes related to, or consistent with the purposes of, any Resource.
Monitoring, Enforcement and Termination
We may, but need not:
Remove or refuse to post any User Contributions for any or no reason in our sole discretion.
Take any action with respect to any User Contribution that we deem necessary or appropriate in our sole discretion, including if we believe that such User Contribution violates these Terms of Use infringes any intellectual property right or other right of any person or entity, threatens the personal safety of users of any Resource or the public, or could create liability for AIAG or others.
Take appropriate legal action, including, without limitation, referral to law enforcement, for any illegal or unauthorized use of any Resource.
Fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing us to disclose the identity or other information of anyone posting any materials on or through any Resource.
Terminate or suspend your access to all or part of any Resource for any violation of these Terms of Use.
Links from a Resource
If a Resource contains links to other Resources and resources provided by third parties, these links are provided for your convenience only. We have no control over the content of those resources and accept no responsibility for them or for any loss or damage that may arise from your use of them. If you decide to access any of the third-party websites linked from a Resource, you do so entirely at your own risk and subject to the Terms of Use of use for such websites.
Terms Specific to the AIAG eCommunity
The AIAG eCommunity permits members and others to collaborate on projects and other matters.
In the course of participating in eCommunity activities, you might have access to the personal information (e.g., name, e-mail address, employer, etc.) of other participants.  You must use such personal information only for the purposes of participating in the AIAG-sanctioned activity within the eCommunity and you must not provide any personal information of any other participant to any non-participant. Please note that forwarding Outlook appointments to non-participants effectively provides the personal information of all invitees to the person to whom you forward the appointment.
Warning regarding Other Users of Resources
WE DO NOT INVESTIGATE OR VET ANY USERS OF ANY RESOURCE.  YOU SHOULD NOT ASSUME THAT ANY INFORMATION YOU RECEIVE THROUGH ANY RESOURCE FROM ANY OTHER PERSON IS TRUE, ACCURATE, OR VERIFIED BY ANYONE.  YOU USE THE RESOURCES AT YOUR OWN RISK.  WE ARE NOT, AND WILL NOT BE, LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY DAMAGES, COSTS, SUITS, ACTIONS, LOSSES, OR ANY OTHER HARM THAT RESULTS FROM ANY ACT OR OMISSION OF ANY OTHER PERSON, WHETHER A USER OF A RESOURCE OR OTHERWISE.
Disclaimer of Warranties and Limitation of Liability
YOUR USE OF ANY RESOURCE, ITS CONTENT, AND RESULTS OF THE USE OF ANY RESOURCE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. EACH RESOURCE, ITS CONTENT, AND ANY RESULTS OBTAINED USING ANY RESOURCE ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS, WITHOUT ANY WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT, NON-INTERFERENCE, AND FITNESS FOR ANY PURPOSE.  WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, NEITHER AIAG NOR ANY PERSON ASSOCIATED WITH AIAG MAKES ANY REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY WITH RESPECT TO THE COMPLETENESS, SECURITY, RELIABILITY, QUALITY, ACCURACY, OR AVAILABILITY OF ANY RESOURCE OR REPRESENTS OR WARRANTS THAT ANY RESOURCE, ITS CONTENT, OR ANY RESULT OF USE OF ANY RESOURCE WILL BE ACCURATE, RELIABLE, ERROR-FREE OR UNINTERRUPTED, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, THAT ANY RESOURCE IS FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS, OR THAT ANY RESOURCE OR ANY SERVICES OR RESULT OF USING ANY RESOURCE WILL OTHERWISE MEET YOUR NEEDS OR EXPECTATIONS.
IN NO EVENT WILL AIAG OR ANY OF AIAG’S DIRECT OR INDIRECT AFFILIATES,  LICENSORS, SERVICE PROVIDERS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, TRUSTEES BE LIABLE FOR DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY OF ANY KIND, UNDER ANY LEGAL THEORY, ARISING OUT OF, OR IN CONNECTION WITH, ANY USE OF, OR INABILITY TO USE, ANY RESOURCE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PERSONAL INJURY, PAIN AND SUFFERING, EMOTIONAL DISTRESS, LOSS OF REVENUE, LOSS OF PROFITS, LOSS OF BUSINESS OR ANTICIPATED SAVINGS, LOSS OF USE, LOSS OF GOODWILL, OR LOSS OF DATA, AND WHETHER CAUSED BY TORT (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, NEGLIGENCE), BREACH OF CONTRACT, OR OTHERWISE.
THE DISCLAIMERS OF WARRANTIES AND LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY IN THESE TERMS OF USE ARE EFFECTIVE EVEN THOUGH A PARTY KNEW OR SHOULD HAVE KNOWN OF THE POSSIBILITY OF ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND AND EVEN THOUGH ONE OR MORE DISCLAIMERS OR LIMITATIONS CAUSES A REMEDY TO FAIL OF ITS ESSENTIAL PURPOSE.
Indemnification
To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, you agree to defend, indemnify, and hold harmless AIAG and AIAG’s direct and indirect affiliates, licensors, and service providers, and its and their respective officers, directors, trustees, employees, contractors, agents, licensors, suppliers, successors and assigns from and against any claims, liabilities, damages, judgments, awards, losses, costs, expenses or fees (including, but not limited to, reasonable attorneys' fees) arising out of or relating to:
Your violation of these Terms of Use;
Your breach of any representation or warranty in these Terms of Use, including, but not limited to, the representation or warranty of any individual that the individual can, and does, bind any organization to these Terms of Use;
Your User Contributions;
Any actual or alleged violation of law resulting from your use of any Resource;
Your use of, reliance upon, and/or transfer of any Resource content, services, or products other than as expressly authorized in these Terms of Use; or
Your use of any information obtained from, or using, a Resource.
CAN-SPAM, Telephone Consumer Protection Act and Similar Law.
Your use of a Resource establishes a business or other applicable relationship with us for purposes of CAN-SPAM, the Telephone Consumer Protection Act, and all other applicable law that addresses unsolicited commercial communications.  By accessing, or continuing to access, any Resource, you agree that we or our agents may call, e-mail, or otherwise communicate with you regarding promotion of the sale, lease, or exchange of goods, services, real property, or any other thing of value.
Governing Law and Jurisdiction
This Agreement shall be governed in all respects by the laws of the State of Michigan without regard for its conflict of laws provisions.
Arbitration
You and we will resolve any dispute or portion thereof arising out of, or in connection with, these Terms of Use or the Privacy Policy by arbitration under the Commercial Arbitration Rules of the American Arbitration Association.
The language of the arbitration will be English;
The place of the arbitration will be Detroit, Michigan;
The parties will cause the arbitrator(s) to, to the maximum extent permitted by the applicable rules, permit participation in the arbitration by remote means, including, but not limited to, videoconference and teleconference; and
The judgment and award of the arbitrator(s) may be entered in, and enforced by, any court of competent jurisdiction.
If, for any reason a claim proceeds in court rather than in arbitration, you and we waive any right to a jury trial, unless such waiver is unenforceable. This means that any claim would be decided by a judge, not a jury.
BY AGREEING TO ARBITRATION, YOU AND WE UNDERSTAND THAT EACH IS AGREEING TO WAIVE ITS RIGHT TO SUE OR GO TO COURT TO ASSERT OR DEFEND RIGHTS UNDER THESE TERMS OF USE OR THE PRIVACY POLICY. THE RULES IN ARBITRATION ARE DIFFERENT. THERE IS NO JUDGE OR JURY. ALTHOUGH REVIEW IS LIMITED, AN ARBITRATOR CAN AWARD ON AN INDIVIDUAL BASIS THE SAME DAMAGES AND RELIEF AS WOULD BE AVAILABLE IN COURT, AND MUST ENFORCE THE SAME LIMITATIONS STATED IN THESE TERMS AS A COURT WOULD.
Other Provisions
Certain areas and features of Resources might contain Terms of Use specific to those areas and features.  Such Terms of Use are in addition to these Terms of Use and prevail over these Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy only to the extent it is not possible to construe these Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy consistently with such other Terms of Use.
General
No waiver by AIAG of any term or condition set forth in the Terms of Use or the Privacy Policy Terms of Use shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or condition or a waiver of any other term or condition, and any failure of AIAG to assert a right or provision under these Terms of Use or the Privacy Policy shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision.  If any provision of these Terms of Use or the Privacy Policy is invalid, illegal, or unenforceable for any reason, such provision shall be eliminated or limited to the minimum extent such that the remaining provisions of these Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy will continue in full force and effect.
